sup everyone came alone theme stop it
was a [ __ ] in an effort to make
starting today I'm officially on Patrian
that's right time today you can give me
your money but seriously [ __ ] I was
beginning to request time and time and
time again saying k 15 when can I stop
sending you money for your work because
it's so cool and I am crowding out that
today starting today you can buy going
down to link in the description below
there's a link to my opinion page where
you can donate any money and here's the
best part but how much money you donate
you get rewards for example start today
by donating one dollar you get a bionic
picture one dolla that's a steal you can
make that [ __ ] up I couldn't believe it
donate any more than one dollar you
unlock secret special access to my ass
py post bionic videos and pictures and
all the unused content like deleted
scenes from up previous videos I upload
my youtube channel pretty cool if you
ask me don't feel out there all probably
thinking no this is too good to be true
access to some deleted scenes and onions
content even concert out I mean belts
people must be Ben Taylor 5 you are
crazy no that's too good and it probably
is but I'm doing it by subscribing to my
patron you're not only helping me but
but Sonic Underground as a ball come
back on TV someday you just did away win
this oh my God
I mean it's so cool you can donate a
dollar three dollars 5dolls ten dollar
25 bucks 100 bucks and of course the
ultimate one with the greatest rewards
of them are three thousand dollars I
know what's the best part of it [ __ ]
the Lord the Lord changed every month
you always have four to afford to
purchase that is cool I mean getting
about dog videos and pictures and all
the cool Awards then no one else will
get to all but you you that's pretty
cool if you ask me so a member ever
wanna go down to my picking page down
the description below become a member
and show everyone just how much you lost
sock on the ground